乔伊，你在吗?
- 是瑞秋
- 你得跟她谈一谈
不行，经过那晚的事之后感觉 真的太奇怪了
别告诉她我在这里
别吃那个
- 嘿
- 嘿，瑞秋
乔伊在吗?
- 我没有看到他，你呢?
- 没有
或许他我在糖碗里 乔伊? 没有
至少你们能逗彼此笑
- 怎么了?
- 我一直没见过他，自从他说
他怎么...你们知道的...
我不知道 我想他在避我
为什么地板上会有贝果?
- 我们在玩游戏?
- 钱德没穿衣服吗?
像是在玩套圈圈游戏吗?
- 没错
- 什么? 不
好吧，听着，如果你们看到乔伊能不能告诉他...
告诉他我很想他
- 好吧，你听到了吗?
- 是啊，裸体贝果游戏?
我不知道那个洞真的很小
- 你得跟她谈一谈
- 我没办法
你们不知道被拒绝的感觉有多难受
我不知道那种感觉?
我在25岁前一直以为“我爱你”的反应是“哦，天啊”
我没有被拒绝过?
我在减肥营时被拒绝过
天啊，饥饿的孩子们真的很残忍
我该怎么办?
她是瑞秋 你永远都不要跟她说话吗?
那很奇怪，也很可怕 但至少你得试试看
好吧
我忘了这个曾套在你的...
我们没有玩它
老友记 Friends S08E17 本集播出：茶叶算命法
我会看你们的茶叶帮你们算命
- 你会茶叶算命法?
- 我这么做有好几年
后来我放弃 因为我算得太难了
生命的乐趣
就是不可预测性
还有茶叶会让我拉肚子
- 我好了，帮我算吧
- 好的
我看一个梯子
它的意思不是升职就是暴力死亡
我是主厨 我不可能被升职
下一个是谁?
我好了，帮我算
好吧
好吧，我看到一个圈圈
那表示你怀了孩子
或你会做出科学发现
我一直都待在实验室里
- 你的茶叶又告诉你什么呢? 菲比
- 好吧
哇，耶
我会认识一个男人 而且很快
他会是我的梦中情人
或许他不是我昨晚梦到的那个男人
有人看到我的衬衫吗?
它是前开式的衬衫淡鲑鱼色
你是说你的粉红色衬衫吗?
淡鲑鱼色?
不，我没有看到你的粉红色衬衫
我一定把它丢在蒙娜家了我就知道
我想你可以到安泰勒的专卖店（著名休闲服装连锁店）再买一件
它是我最喜欢的衬衫我爱它
请蒙娜把它还给你
我不知道，或许吧
我们不算是好聚好散
我想去她家就得忘了她告诉我的一件事
她要我去跳楼自杀
等一下
我走到哪里都会看到那个男人
我们搭同一班公车去同一家书局
或许他就是我的真命天子
你们看到了吗?
他真的在看你 而且他很帅
我的茶叶出现乡巴佬的图案 那是什么意思?
嗨
嘿
- 嗨
茶叶让菲比拉肚子
我以为乔伊跟我可以不尴尬
但我们不知道该怎么相处
还有我一直都想这么说
如果你们知道这件事 我真的很希望你们提醒我一下
只要给点提示就够了
“乔伊爱你做好准备”
- 抱歉
- 下次别再犯了
- 那真的很难，但情况会有改善的
- 你怎么知道?
如果情况恶化...
但我们无法共处一室呢?
我不善于给好建议
要我讽刺你一下吗?
要起司吗?
甜心，为什么布鲁斯史普林斯汀的CD会放在凯特史帝文斯的盒子里?
如果我找不到正确的盒子 我会随手拿一个盒子来装
- 凯特史帝文斯的CD在哪里?
- 詹姆士泰勒的盒子里
- 那张CD在哪里?
- 我帮你节省一些时间
那200张CD 没有一张放在正确的盒子里
好吧，不需要慌张 大家深呼吸
我们只需要把CD放在正确的盒子里
那么做的话应该能将CD排好
我们得谈一谈这件事
天啊，你们真的有问题 我为你们感到难过
好吧，对不起
你们两个满脑子都是这件令人不舒服的事
改变一下话题
让他谈别的事
对，那挺有道理的
或许你在工作上有问题需要他的建议...
- 我可以那么做
- 很好
《迈阿密风云》（80年代的警察故事肥皂剧）的原声带？ 真的吗？
那是唱片行的赠品
我得拿钱去换
嘿
我真的不知道该跟你说什么
或许乔伊可以帮你解决工作上的大问题
- 什么?
- 对，乔伊，她...
瑞秋工作上有个大问题 那真的很伤脑筋
你知道吗?我们想赶上晚餐预约就得马上出发
对，乔伊 或许你可以帮她
- 好吧
- 你知道吗?
你帮忙解决这个问题时
或许你想手边找些事来说我是不小心想到的...
譬如说将CD放到正确的盒子里
来吧
你工作上出了大问题?
对，那是
真的没什么
好吧
我想我该走了
不，乔伊，等一下，我有问题 它真的很严重，是...
是我的老板
- 是吗?
- 对，跟...
跟我的宝宝
是吗?
我老板想买我的宝宝
什么? 我的天啊
我知道，我跟你说过了 这真的是个大问题
- 他要买你的宝宝?
- 你能相信吗?
- 那太疯狂了
- 我就是那么跟他说的
- 怎么会发生这种事?
- 我会告诉你
我老板跟他太太 他们不孕，所以...．
在圣诞派对上我们碰到了面...
他喝醉了跟我说“瑞秋，我要买下你的宝宝”
你说你老板跟宝宝有问题的时候...
我以为你是指产假的问题
对
对，那样子问题简单多了
- 哈喽
- 是你，我走到哪里都会碰到你
我是吉米，吉米尼尔森
嗨，吉米吉米尼尔森 我是菲比 菲比布非
- 我们最近常见面
- 对
或许明天晚餐时我们也能碰面 八点可以吗?
或许会吧
蒙娜
如果我是鲑鱼色衬衫 我会在哪里?
上游
该死 没有人听到我的好笑话
抱歉我把酒洒到你的衬衫上
- 没关系
- 不，它还是湿的
我得把它拿去洗干挣免得留下印子 我去找件衣服借你
拿去吧
我真的不想穿女人的衬衫
- 那是男人的衬衫
- 可怕的粉红色
那不是粉红色
甜心 我们注定要在一起
- 我们都有安妮的原声带
- 甜心，那都是你买的
谢谢你给我关于乔伊的建议
- 你是工作的问题吗?
- 它真的是太棒了
我觉得他是我的朋友
- 你说你有什么问题?
- 那不重要
重点是我想一切都会没事
需要我效劳吗?
你觉得你可以买走我朋友的宝宝?
我们一直巧遇真的很有趣吧? 那就像是有人要我们在一起
没错，那就是我
聪明的家伙，做的好
- 跟我谈谈你自己
- 好吧，我是按摩师
- 我以前在这个地方工作
- 你喜欢参加派对吗?
我喜欢派对
你很狂野，对吧?
- 对，我猜是有一点
- 那没有什么，我也很狂野
总之...
我住在纽约 我猜那有点狂野
我从14岁就住在这里
抱歉我盯着你不放
因为你有双最漂亮的眼睛
- 别说了
- 还有你的胸部
好吧
听着，你有点太快了
我会解开你的疑虑
宇宙要我们在一起
我们为什么不开始呢? 你可以跟我谈谈你自己
- 好吧
我写小孩子看的...
色情小说
- 什么?
- 它们非常不受欢迎
我的天啊
或许你会想知道 我是个博士
- 真的吗?
- 对，它真的很大
够了
- 嘿
- 乔伊，听我说
谢谢你昨天跟我谈 那对我来说意义重大
别客气 我得告诉你
那家伙不会再为了宝宝的事来烦你了
- 什么?
- 就说我已经解决了问题
我们得谈一谈
别担心，我好好地跟他谈过
“你不能买别人的宝宝 别闹了”
- 什么?
不
他不想买我的宝宝 那是我编出来的
什么? 为什么?
我们才有话题聊
你想不出来别的藉口吗？
你说你老板要买你的宝宝?
你对我老板大叫 我会被开除，我该怎么办?
你可以卖掉你的宝宝
我不敢相信你会去找我老板 我会被开除
- 你骗我
- 是她要我那么做的
钱德有两张安妮的原声带
我的天啊
- 罗斯
- 哈喽
你在做什么?
希望你们听了能够释怀 我没有自摸
好吧，我会打电话给你
早安，你找我?
请进，坐下
- 听着，佐纳先生
- 让我先说吧
好吧
人事部的李将是我们谈话的见证人
天啊
如果我有暗示过你 我想买你的宝宝...
我很抱歉，好吗?
上星期我问你 你的预产期是什么时候
我并没有那个意思要告诉你我想“买”你的宝宝
我希望清楚地告诉你...
我了解 它是你的宝宝
我不能买下它
只要把话说清楚就好了
到了
- 这不是你常去的洗衣店
- 我知道
那个怪胎会去那里 我得找新的洗衣店
我还得找新的银行 成人书店，杂货店...
- 什么?
- 新的杂货店
宇宙说我会认识一个好男人 那是真的吗?
我上天堂后 一定会痛扁它
你会认识某人的 如果我能找到好男人，你也可以
对，我们都可以，也都会做到
- 你不必进来
- 你在开玩笑吗?
他们在这里把衣服洗干净 对我来说这就像是迪士尼乐园
我要到这里看干净衬衫跳舞
对不起 我想你掉了
- 哇
- 什么?
抱歉 你真的是美得不可思议
我也这么觉得 但又能怎么办呢?
别觉得我疯了 我本来是要帮你捡这个
- 你相信那种事吗?
- 有一点
你说的对
- 你要去喝咖啡吗?
- 我很乐意，我去跟我朋友说一声
是墨水印子 我能看你把它洗干净吗?
她一定是离开了
- 所以呢? 发生了什么事?
- 没事了
他们很高兴我不告他们 我还能多放一个月领薪产假
只要我知道那些钱绝不是...
这个宝宝或其他宝宝的订金
拉夫罗兰真的想尽办法...
要证明他们不是贩婴集团
- 能让我们独处一下吗?
- 你要把我踢出我家的客厅
对
我会在那里
抱歉我骗了你 我只是希望事情
我知道
你的方法的确有效
我不知道你是怎么想的 但我一直没想到我们的事
对，你说的对
对，我们又恢复了“朋友”的样子
- 我喜欢，我很想念那段时光
- 我也是
我没有想到自己怎么会...
跟你说那些话你跟我的感觉不同
那真的很可怕
我的妇产科医生想杀我
编号是J437- A
颜色，冬莓色
听着 过来，来吧...
关于昨天的事我很抱歉
但我不是跟你说过不要在门外留备份钥匙吗?
还好那是我 不是别人
我想那么说太重了一点
总之蒙娜，我真的很抱歉 那只是...
听着，你不必道歉 我了解你为什么会去那里
- 真的吗?
- 对，你还对我有感觉
老实说 我也对你还有感觉
我希望我们能复合 那是不可能的
你跟瑞秋还有宝宝的事太复杂了，我只是...
那个人不该是我
天啊，你说的对
罗斯，我们得坚强
好吧，我得走了
我能留下它来怀念你吗?
不行
Joey? Are you in there?
- That's Rachel.
- You have to talk to her.
I can't. Not after the other night.
It's too weird.
Don't tell her I'm here.
Don't eat that!
- Hey!
- Hey, Rachel.
Is Joey here?
- I don't see him. You?
- No.
Maybe he's in the sugar bowl. Joey?
Nope.
Well, at least you make each other laugh.
- What's up?
- I haven't seen him since he said...
...how he, you know...
I don't know, I think he's avoiding me.
Why is that bagel on the floor?
- We were playing a game.
- Was Chandler naked?
Sort of like a ring-toss kind of situation?
- Sure!
- What? No! No!
- All right, listen.
- If you see Joey, will you just tell him that...?
Tell him I miss him.
- Okay. Did you hear that?
- Yeah. That naked bagel game?
Dude, I don't know.
That's a pretty small hole.
- You've gotta talk to her.
- I can't.
You guys don't know what it's like to get shot down.
I don't know what that's like?
Until I was 25, I thought the response to "I love you" was "Oh, crap."
No rejection?
I got shot down at fat camp.
Boy, kids are mean when they're hungry.
So, what do I do?
It's Rachel. You're gonna never talk to her again?
It's weird and it's awkward, but you gotta at least try.
Yeah, okay.
I forgot this was on your...
We didn't play it!
The One With The Tea Leaves
I'll look at your tea leaves and tell your fortune.
- You read tea leaves?
- I've done it for years.
I actually stopped because I was so accurate.
And one of the great joys of life...
...is its wondrous unpredictability, you know?
And also, tea tends to give me the trots.
- Okay. I'm done. Read mine.
- Okay.
I see a ladder.
Which can mean either a promotion or a violent death.
I'm the head chef. I can't get promoted.
Who's next?
I'm done. Do mine.
Okay.
Oh! Okay, I see a circle.
Which can either mean you're having a baby...
...or you'll make a scientific discovery!
Well, I have been spending a lot of time in the lab.
- What does yours say, Pheebs?
- All right.
Wow! Yay!
Oh, I'm gonna meet a guy! And really soon!
He's gonna be the man of my dreams.
Probably not the guy I had a dream about last night.
Has anyone seen my shirt?
It's a button-down, like a faded salmon color?
You mean your pink shirt?
Faded salmon color?
No, I haven't seen your pink shirt.
I must have left it at Mona's. I knew it!
I'm sure you can get another one at Ann Taylor's.
That's my favorite shirt. I love it.
Ask Mona to give it back.
I don't know. I could.
We didn't really end things on good terms.
If I went, I'd be ignoring the one thing she asked me to do...
...jump up my own ass and die.
Oh, wait a second, you guys?
I've been seeing that guy everywhere I go.
We take the same bus, go to the same bookstore.
Maybe he's the tea guy.
Did you see that?
He totally checked you out! And he is so cute!
Mine is a picture of the Village People. What does that mean?
Hi.
Hey.
- Hi.
Tea gives Phoebe the trots!
I thought Joey and I would be okay...
...but we don't know how to be together.
By the way, I've been meaning to say this.
If you guys knew about this, a heads-up would have been nice.
Just a little, you know.
"Joey loves you. Be prepared."
- Sorry.
- Well, for next time.
- It's tough, but things will improve.
- How do you know?
What if it gets worse and worse...
...to the point where we can't be in the same room?
I'm not great at the advice.
Can I interest you in a sarcastic comment?
Some cheese?
Honey, why is the Bruce Springsteen CD in the Cat Stevens case?
If I can't find the right case, I use the nearest one.
- Where is the Cat Stevens CD?
- The James Taylor case.
- Where is that CD?
- I'll save you time.
Two hundred CDs, not one of them in the right case.
Okay. No need to panic.
Deep breaths, everyone.
We'll just have to put the CDs in their right cases.
If we do that, we should come up with some kind of order.
We have to talk this through.
Oh, my God, you have such problems! I feel so terrible for you!
All right. Okay, I'm sorry.
You're both focusing on this uncomfortable thing.
Change the subject.
Get him talking about something else.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Maybe you need his advice on a work problem...
- I could do that.
- Good.
The Miami Vice soundtrack? Really?
They were just giving those away at the store.
In exchange for money.
Hey.
I really don't know what to tell you.
Maybe Joey could help you out with your big work problem.
- What?
- Yeah, Joey, she's...
Rachel's got this big work problem.
It is a head-scratcher.
Know what? If we're gonna make dinner, we're gonna have to leave.
Yeah, Joey, maybe you could help her out.
- Okay.
- Oh, and you know what?
While you're helping solve this problem...
...you might want to do something with your hands.
Like, off the top of my head...
...maybe put the CDs in their right cases.
Here we go.
So you have a big work problem?
Yeah. It's, uh...
Yeah, it's, uh...
You know, it's nothing.
Okay.
So I think I'm gonna take off.
No, wait, Joey, it is.
It's something. It's...
It's my boss.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. And, uh...
And my baby.
Yeah?
My boss wants to buy my baby.
What? Oh, my God!
I know, I told you, it's a really big problem!
- He wants to buy your baby?
- Can you believe that?
- That's crazy.
- That's what I told him!
- How did this even happen?
- Well, I'll tell you.
See, my boss and his wife, they can't have children, so...
And then when we were at the Christmas party...
...he got drunk and said to me, "Rachel, I want to buy your baby."
When you said it was a problem about your boss and the baby...
...I figured it was about maternity leave.
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah, that would have been a much simpler problem.
- Oh, hello.
- Oh, it's you. I see you everywhere.
I'm Jim. Jim Nelson.
Hi, Jim-Jim Nelson.
I'm Phoebe-Phoebe Buffay.
- We've seen each other a lot lately.
- Yes.
Maybe we'll see each other at dinner tomorrow.
Around 8:00?
Well, maybe we will.
Mona?
Okay, if I were a salmon shirt, where would I be?
Upstream.
Damn, nobody's here for my good ones.
I am so sorry I spilled wine all over your shirt.
- It's okay.
- No, it's still wet.
Let me get it out before it sets.
I have something you could wear.
Here.
I don't know if I want to wear a womars shirt.
- That's a mars shirt.
- Awfully pink.
It's not pink!
Honey, we are so meant to be together.
- We both have the Annie soundtrack.
- Honey, both yours.
Hey, great advice on that Joey thing.
- The work problem?
- It was perfect.
It felt like he was my friend.
- What problem did you say you have?
- Oh, that's not important.
The point is, I think everything's gonna be okay.
May I help you?
You think you can just buy my friend's baby?
Isn't it funny how we kept meeting?
It's as if someone wants us together.
Someone does. Me.
Witty banter. Well done. Good.
- Tell me a little bit about yourself.
- Okay. I'm a masseuse.
- And I used to work at this place...
- Do you like to party?
I like parties.
You're wild, aren't you?
- Yeah, I guess. A little.
- Ain't no thing. I'm wild too.
So anyway...
...l've lived in New York, somewhat wildly, I guess...
...for, well, since I was 14.
I'm sorry. I'm staring.
It's just that you have the most beautiful eyes.
- Oh, stop it.
- And your breasts!
Okay.
Look, you're coming on a little strong.
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
The universe wants us to be together.
Why don't we start over?
You can tell me about yourself.
- All right.
- Okay.
I write erotic novels...
...for children.
- What?
- They're wildly unpopular.
Oh, my God!
Also, you might like to know I have a Ph. D.
- Wow! You do?
- Yep. A pretty huge...
All right.
- Hey.
- Joey, honey, listen.
Thanks for talking to me yesterday.
It meant a lot.
Not a problem. Just so you know...
...that guy won't be bothering you about that baby thing anymore.
- What?
- Let's just say I took care of it.
Let's say more.
Don't worry. I told him, very nicely:
"You don't go buying people's babies! So back off!"
- What?
No, no, no!
He doesn't want to buy my baby!
I made that up!
What? Why?
So we would have something to talk about!
And you couldn't think of anything else?
You said your boss wants to buy your baby?
You yelled at my boss!
I'll lose my job! What am I gonna do?
You could always sell your baby.
I can't believe you brought my boss into it! I'll be fired!
- You lied to me!
- Well, she told me to!
Chandler has two copies of Annie!
Oh, my God!
- Ross!
- Hello!
What are you doing?
Not touching myself, if that makes anyone less uncomfortable.
Okay, then. I'll call you.
Morning. You wanted to see me?
Please, come in. Have a seat.
- Look, Mr. Zelner...
- It's best I speak first.
Yeah.
Lee from Human Resources is here as a witness to our conversation.
Oh, God.
If I in any way implied that I wanted to buy your baby...
...I am sorry. Okay?
Last week, when I asked you when your due date was...
...I certainly did not mean that I felt that I was "due" your baby.
I want to be very clear...
...that I understand that it's your baby...
...and it is not mine to purchase.
Well, as long as we are clear about that.
There it is.
- Not your regular cleaners.
- I know.
That creep goes there. I had to find a new one.
I have to find a new bank, adult bookstore, grocery store...
- What?
- A new grocery store.
The universe said I'd meet a nice guy.
I got that?
When I get up there, I'm gonna kick some ass.
You'll meet someone.
If I can meet a great guy, so can you.
Yeah, we both can. And we both will.
- You didn't have to come in.
- You kidding?
This is where they get out stains.
This is like Disneyland for me.
I'm gonna be over here watching the dance of the clean shirts.
Excuse me. I think you dropped...
- Wow!
- What?
Sorry. You're just so incredibly beautiful.
Well, I'm sorry about that too. But what are you gonna do?
Don't think I'm crazy, but I was meant to pick this up.
- Do you believe in that kind of thing?
- A little.
Now you're talking.
- Want to go for coffee?
- I'd love to. Let me tell my friend.
An ink stain! Can I watch how you get this out?
She must have left.
- So? What happened?
- It's all gonna be okay.
They're so happy I'm not suing, I got an extra month paid maternity leave.
So long as I understand the money should not be construed...
...as a down payment on this or any other child.
Ralph Lauren is going out of their way...
...to show they're not in the baby-buying business.
- Give us a minute?
- Kicking me out of my living room?
Yeah.
I'll be in there.
I'm sorry I lied to you. I was just trying to make things...
I know. I know.
It kind of worked.
I don't know about you, but I haven't thought about our thing.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah. It's kind of been like "us" again, a little bit.
- Yeah, I know. I've missed that.
- Me too.
I haven't thought about how I put myself out there...
...and said that stuff. How you didn't feel the same...
...and how it was really awkward.
My gynecologist tried to kill me.
Item J437-A.
Color: Winterberry.
Hi, listen. Come here. Come...
I'm so, so sorry about yesterday.
But what did I tell you about leaving your key outside the door like that?
I mean, you're lucky it was me and not someone else.
I guess lucky is too strong a word.
Anyway, Mona, I'm really, really sorry.
It's just...
Listen, you don't have to apologize.
I understand why you were there.
- You do?
- Yeah. You still have feelings for me.
To be honest, I still have feelings for you.
I wish we could work it out, but we can't.
It's too complicated with you and Rachel and the baby. I just...
It just wasn't meant to be.
Oh, God. You're right.
Ross, we have to be strong.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
Can I ? To remember you?
No.